Guide to the William Manchester Papers, 1934 - 2004
William Manchester Papers1934 - 2004
- Series IV: Correspondence
  - Kennedy family and related correspondence
    - Kennedy, John F., 1961-1975 and undated (Box 263, Folder 7)
    - Kennedy, Joseph II, 1996 (Box 263, Folder 8)
    - Kennedy, Robert, 1964-1993 and undated (Box 263, Folder 9)
    - Lincoln, Evelyn, 1971 (Box 263, Folder 10)
    - Shriver, Eunice, 1967-1983 and undated (Box 263, Folder 11)
    - Shriver, Sargent, 1968-1975 (Box 263, Folder 12)
    - Other correspondence, 1964-1996 and undated (Box 263, Folder 13-18)
  - Philby, H.A.R. Kim, 1978 (Box 263, Folder 19)
- Series V: Personal papers
  - Early papers
    - 1937-1940, 1944 (Box 263, Folder 20)
    - Massachusetts State College
      - 1940-1942 (Box 263, Folder 21)
      - Freshman themes, 1940-1941 (Box 263, Folder 22)
      - 1943-1946 (Box 263, Folder 23)
      - Graduation, 1946 (Box 263, Folder 24)
      - Graduation, 1946 (Box 264, Folder 1)
      - 1946, undated (Box 264, Folder 2)
      - Report cards, 1940-1946, 1954 (Box 264, Folder 3)
    - Dartmouth College, 1943 (Box 264, Folder 4)
    - U.S. Naval Hospital, 1945 (Box 264, Folder 5)
    - Writings, 1945-1946 (Box 264, Folder 6)
    - Columbia University, Graduate School of Journalism, application essay, 1946 (Box 264, Folder 7)
    - University of Missouri
      - 1946-1947 (Box 264, Folder 8)
      - Contemporary Problems of a Police Reporter, 1946-1947 (Box 264, Folder 9)
      - A Report of the First Semester's Work in Preparing a Thesis on the Subject, A Study of H.L. Mencken and The Smart Set Magazine, 1946 (Box 264, Folder 10)
      - A Study of H.L. Mencken and The Smart Set Magazine, 1947 (Box 264, Folder 11)
      - Diploma, 1947 (Box 264, Folder 12)
  - Addresses and address books (Box 265, Folder 1-6)
  - Addresses, 1950s (Box 265, Folder 7)
  - Appraisal of papers, circa 1989 (Box 266, Folder 1-2)
  - Articles written by Mr. Manchester, ca. 1964 (Box 266, Folder 3)
  - Assassination Records Review Board, 1996 (Box 266, Folder 4)
    - McCone, John, 1996 (Box 266, Folder 5)
    - Hoover, J. Edgar, 1996 (Box 266, Folder 6)
    - Manchester, William, 1996 (Box 266, Folder 7)
    - Salinger, Pierre [restricted], 1996 (Box 470)
    - Lovelady, Billy, 1996 (Box 266, Folder 8)
    - Sanders, Barefoot, 1996 (Box 266, Folder 9)
    - Curry, Jesse, 1996 (Box 266, Folder 10)
    - Hosty, James, 1996 (Box 266, Folder 11)
    - Peterson, William, 1996 (Box 266, Folder 12)
    - Greer, Bill [restricted], 1996 (Box 470)
    - Manchester, William [restricted], 1996 (Box 470)
    - Novello, Angela [restricted], 1996 (Box 470)
    - Katzenbach, Nicholas, 1996 (Box 266, Folder 13)
    - Sawyer, Herbert, 1996 (Box 266, Folder 14)
    - Johns, Lem [restricted], 1996 (Box 470)
    - Manchester, William, 1996 (Box 266, Folder 15)
    - Wilson, Frank J., 1996 (Box 266, Folder 16)
    - Manchester, William, 1996 (Box 266, Folder 17)
    - Warren, Earl, 1996 (Box 266, Folder 18)
    - Bruno, Gerry, 1996 (Box 266, Folder 19)
    - Behn, Gerald [restricted], 1996 (Box 470)
    - Bachelor, Charles, 1996 (Box 266, Folder 20)
    - Bundy, McGeorge, 1996 (Box 266, Folder 21)
    - Dillon, C. Douglas, 1996 (Box 266, Folder 22)
    - Foster, Bob [restricted], 1996 (Box 470)
    - Burkley, George [restricted], 1996 (Box 470)
    - Connally, Mrs. John B., 1996 (Box 266, Folder 23)
    - Cretian, Paul, 1996 (Box 266, Folder 24)
    - Truly, Roy S., 1996 (Box 266, Folder 25)
    - Walker, Edwin, 1996 (Box 266, Folder 26)
    - Manchester, William, 1996 (Box 266, Folder 27)
    - Sawyer, Herbert, 1996 (Box 266, Folder 28)
    - Sanders, Barefoot, 1996 (Box 266, Folder 29)
    - Manchester, William, 1996 (Box 266, Folder 30)
    - Skelton, Byron, 1996 (Box 266, Folder 31)
    - Youngblood, Rufus [restricted], 1996 (Box 470)
    - Connally, John, 1996 (Box 266, Folder 32)
    - Whaley, William, 1996 (Box 266, Folder 33)
    - Paine, Ruth & Michael, 1996 (Box 266, Folder 34)
    - Valenti, Jack, 1996 (Box 266, Folder 35)
    - Gonzalez, Henry, 1996 (Box 266, Folder 36)
    - Smith, Steve [restricted], 1996 (Box 470)
    - Sorrels, Forest V., 1996 (Box 266, Folder 37)
  - Atomic bomb, 1985 (Box 266, Folder 38)
  - Awards and honors
    - 1950-1952 (Box 266, Folder 39)
    - University of Massachusetts, 1965 (Box 266, Folder 40)
    - University of Massachusetts, 1965 (Box 267, Folder 1-3)
    - Prix International Dag Hammarskjoeld, 1967 (Box 267, Folder 4)
    - 1968 (Box 267, Folder 5)
    - University of Missouri, 1969 (Box 267, Folder 6-8)
    - 1969-1975 (Box 267, Folder 9)
    - University of New Haven, 1979 (Box 267, Folder 10)
    - 1980-1981 (Box 268, Folder 1)
    - Middletown Commission on the Arts, 1981 (Box 268, Folder 2)
    - Wesleyan University, 1981 (Box 268, Folder 3)
    - University of Detroit, 1981 (Box 268, Folder 4)
    - University of Massachusetts, 1982 (Box 268, Folder 5)
    - American Academy of Achievement, 1984 (Box 268, Folder 6)
    - Skidmore College, 1987 (Box 268, Folder 7-8)
    - University of Richmond, 1988 (Box 268, Folder 9-10)
    - University of Richmond, degree, 1988 (Box shelf)
    - Literacy Volunteers of Connecticut, 1990 (Box 268, Folder 11)
    - Russell Sage College, 1990 (Box 268, Folder 12)
    - Wesleyan University, 1992 (Box 269, Folder 1)
    - Sarah Josepha Hale, 1993 (Box 269, Folder 2)
    - Wesleyan University, 2002 (Box 269, Folder 3)
    - Undated (Box 269, Folder 4)
  - Baltimore Press Club, 1950 (Box 269, Folder 5)
  - Baltimore Sunpapers, 1951-1952, undated (Box 269, Folder 6)
    - Foreign correspondent
      - Journal, 1953 Mar 7-Apr 28 (Box 269, Folder 7)
      - Journal, 1953 Mar 26-Apr 6 (Box 269, Folder 8)
      - Journal, 1953 Jun 7-13 (Box 269, Folder 9)
      - Journal, 1953 13-29 (Box 269, Folder 10)
      - Journal, India, 1953 (Box 269, Folder 11)
      - Turkey, writings and notes, 1953 (Box 269, Folder 12)
      - Turkey, 1953 (Box 269, Folder 13)
      - Egypt, writings and notes, 1953 (Box 269, Folder 14-16)
      - Egypt, 1953 (Box 270, Folder 1-3)
      - India, 1953 (Box 270, Folder 4-5)
      - Southeast Asia, writings and notes, 1953 (Box 270, Folder 6)
      - Southeast Asia, 1953 (Box 270, Folder 7)
      - India, Thailand, and Burma, 1953 (Box 270, Folder 8)
      - Vietnam, 1953 (Box 270, Folder 9-10)
  - Battle of Okinawa Historical Society, 1995 (Box 270, Folder 11)
  - Bicentennial Minutes [CBS Television], 1974 (Box 270, Folder 12)
  - Book-of-the-Month Club 60th anniversary dinner, 1986 (Box 270, Folder 13)
  - Bookcase, undated (Box 270, Folder 14)
  - Books I have enjoyed, 1961 (Box 270, Folder 15)
  - Bulletin board items, 1990s (Box 270, Folder 16)
  - Calendar, 1967 (Box 270, Folder 17)
  - Calendar, 1968 (Box 271, Folder 1)
  - Calendar, 1969 (Box 271, Folder 2)
  - Calendar, 1985 (Box 271, Folder 3)
  - City of Anger list of people to receive inscribed copies, 1986 (Box 271, Folder 4)
  - Conversational Spanish, 1969 (Box 271, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, press releases, Gainer, Krupp, Death
    - 1961-1966 (Box 271, Folder 6)
    - 1967 (Box 271, Folder 7)
    - 1968 (Box 271, Folder 8)
    - 1969, undated (Box 271, Folder 9)
  - Courses taught
    - Wesleyan, Non-Fiction Prose, ENGL 164, 1968-1969 (Box 271, Folder 10-13)
    - Corning Community College, 1978 (Box 271, Folder 14-15)
  - Critic: A proposal for a new magazine, undated (Box 271, Folder 16)
  - Critical comments, 1967 (Box 271, Folder 17)
  - Critical digest, 1959 (Box 272, Folder 1)
  - Date book, 1956 (Box 272, Folder 2)
  - Date book, 1986 (Box 272, Folder 3)
  - Dust jackets, 1950s-80s (Box 272, Folder 4)
  - Evening Sun, Sunpapers, 1984-1987 (Box 272, Folder 5)
  - FDR, 1968-1969 (Box 272, Folder 6)
  - Federal Bureau of Investigation
    - 1980 (Box 272, Folder 7)
    - 1955-1964 (Box 272, Folder 8)
    - 1958 (Box 272, Folder 9)
    - 1964-1967 (Box 272, Folder 10-11)
  - File labels (Box 272, Folder 12)
  - Financial
    - 1950-1959 (Box 272, Folder 13)
    - 1960-1969 (Box 272, Folder 14)
    - 1970-1979 (Box 272, Folder 15)
    - 1980-1989 (Box 272, Folder 16)
    - 1990-1996 (Box 273, Folder 1)
    - 1997-2000, undated (Box 273, Folder 2)
    - Appraisal, 316 Pine St., 2003 (Box 273, Folder 3)
    - Automobile accidents, 1991-1996 (Box 273, Folder 4)
    - Bank, main file
      - 1968-1969 (Box 273, Folder 5)
      - 1970 (Box 273, Folder 6)
      - 1971 (Box 273, Folder 7)
      - 1972 (Box 273, Folder 8)
      - 1973-1974, undated (Box 273, Folder 9)
    - Bank
      - 1968 (Box 273, Folder 10)
      - 1969 (Box 273, Folder 11)
      - 1970, 1972, undated (Box 273, Folder 12)
    - Bank, general
      - 1971-1979 (Box 273, Folder 13)
      - 1980 (Box 273, Folder 14)
      - 1981 Jan-Jun (Box 273, Folder 15)
      - 1979-1981 (Box 274, Folder 1)
      - 1982 (Box 274, Folder 2-3)
      - 1983, undated (Box 274, Folder 4)
    - Bank, general (from office)
      - 1972-1974 (Box 274, Folder 5)
      - 1975 (Box 274, Folder 6)
      - 1976 (Box 274, Folder 7)
      - 1977 (Box 274, Folder 8)
    - Bank-Office, brought home 1/21/80
      - 1962-1977 (Box 274, Folder 9)
      - 1978 (Box 274, Folder 10)
      - 1979, undated (Box 274, Folder 11)
    - Blue Cross, 1982-1986 (Box 274, Folder 12)
    - Check register, 1990-1996 (Box 274, Folder 13)
    - Check register, 1996-1997 (Box 275, Folder 1)
    - Credit cards, 1995-1996 (Box 275, Folder 2)
    - Income tax
      - 1948-1949 (Box 275, Folder 3)
      - 1950-1959 (Box 275, Folder 4)
      - 1960-1969 (Box 275, Folder 5)
      - 1970-1971, 1977 (Box 275, Folder 6)
      - 1981-1983 (Box 275, Folder 7)
    - Insurance
      - 316 Pine St., 1990-2002 (Box 275, Folder 8)
      - Automobile, 1990-2003 (Box 275, Folder 9)
      - Automobile, extra, 1990-1994 (Box 275, Folder 10)
      - Longboat Key, 1978-1999 (Box 275, Folder 11)
      - Other, 1966, 1992, 1994 (Box 275, Folder 12)
      - Personal items, 1990-2001 (Box 275, Folder 13)
      - Workers compensation, 1990-1993 (Box 276, Folder 1)
    - Investments
      - 1967-1978 (Box 276, Folder 2)
      - 1995-1997 (Box 276, Folder 3)
      - 1995-1996 (Box 276, Folder 4)
    - Longboat Key, 1978-1999 (Box 276, Folder 5)
    - Net worth, dead file, 1972-1973 (Box 276, Folder 6)
    - Postage receipts, 1990-1992 (Box 276, Folder 7)
    - Royalty reports-1
      - 1949-1956 (Box 276, Folder 8)
      - 1957-1959 (Box 276, Folder 9)
      - 1960-1962 (Box 276, Folder 10)
      - 1963-1966 (Box 276, Folder 11)
      - 1967 (Box 276, Folder 12)
      - 1968 (Box 276, Folder 13)
    - Royalty reports-2
      - 1965-1968 (Box 277, Folder 1)
      - 1969 (Box 277, Folder 2)
      - 1970 (Box 277, Folder 3)
      - 1971 (Box 277, Folder 4)
    - Royalty reports (B)
      - 1971 (Box 277, Folder 5)
      - 1972 (Box 277, Folder 6)
      - 1973 (Box 277, Folder 7)
      - 1974 (Box 277, Folder 8)
    - Royalty reports-4
      - 1971-1974 (Box 277, Folder 9)
      - 1975 (Box 277, Folder 10)
      - 1976-1977 (Box 277, Folder 11)
    - Royalty reports-5
      - 1977-1978 (Box 277, Folder 12)
      - 1979 (Box 277, Folder 13)
      - 1980-1981 (Box 277, Folder 14)
    - Royalties, 1994-2001 (Box 277, Folder 15)
    - Royalties, USSR, 1968-1972 (Box 277, Folder 16)
    - Tax appraisal matter, 1967-1974 (Box 278, Folder 1-4)
    - Taxes, 1974-1993 (Box 278, Folder 5)
    - Tax - Longboat Key, 1997 (Box 278, Folder 6)
    - Traveler's checks, 1968-1987, undated (Box 278, Folder 7)
  - Florida, 1989-1998 (Box 278, Folder 8)
  - Genealogy (Box 278, Folder 9)
  - General - 2, 1955-1957 (Box 278, Folder 10)
  - General - 3, 1958-1959 (Box 278, Folder 11-14)
  - General, 1959-1961 (Box 278, Folder 15)
  - General - 7, 1968 (Box 278, Folder 16)
  - General - 8, 1968 (Box 279, Folder 1-2)
  - General - 9, 1968-1969 (Box 279, Folder 3)
  - General - 10, 1969 (Box 279, Folder 4)
  - General - 11, 1965-1981 (Box 279, Folder 5)
  - General A, 1977 (Box 279, Folder 6)
  - General D, 1978-1979 (Box 279, Folder 7)
  - General E, 1979-1980 (Box 279, Folder 8)
  - General F, 1980 (Box 279, Folder 9)
  - General G, 1981 (Box 279, Folder 10)
  - General H, 1981 (Box 279, Folder 11)
  - General, 1981-1984 (Box 279, Folder 12)
  - General, 1984 (Box 279, Folder 13)
  - General AAA-1, 1984-1985 (Box 279, Folder 14)
  - General AAA-2, 1985-1986 (Box 279, Folder 15)
  - General B, 1985-1987 (Box 280, Folder 1)
  - General, 1987-1988 (Box 280, Folder 2)
  - General, 1988 (Box 280, Folder 3)
  - The Gridiron Club annual dinner, 1967 (Box 280, Folder 4)
  - Guggenheim Fellowship, 1958 (Box 280, Folder 5)
  - Guggenheim Fellowship, 1959-1963 (Box 280, Folder 6)
  - H L M, 1990 (Box 280, Folder 7)
  - H. L. Mencken (Box 280, Folder 8-9)
  - House-1, 1955-1968 (Box 280, Folder 10-15)
  - House-2, 1968-1972 (Box 281, Folder 1)
  - House-3, 1968-1980 (Box 281, Folder 2)
  - Index of documents (Box 281, Folder 3)
  - Instrument of Surrender 1945, facsimilie (Box shelf)
  - John Hopkins University, 1984 (Box 281, Folder 4)
  - Legal
    - Agents and editors, 1999-2003 (Box 281, Folder 5)
    - The Arms of Krupp
      - Injunctions, 1968-1969 (Box 281, Folder 6)
      - BMW, 1969 (Box 281, Folder 7)
    - CCLU v. Sanders et. al., 1969 (Box 281, Folder 8)
    - Contracts
      - 1969, 1979, [1981?] (Box 281, Folder 9)
      - American Caesar, 1975-1986 (Box 281, Folder 10)
      - The Arms of Krupp, 1964-1975 (Box 281, Folder 11)
      - The Arms of Krupp; America, America; Collected Essays, 1970 (Box 281, Folder 12)
      - The Arms of Krupp, Goodbye, Darkness, 2002 (Box 281, Folder 13)
      - Beard the Lion, 1957-1958 (Box 281, Folder 14)
      - City of Anger, 1952-1969 (Box 281, Folder 15)
      - The Death of a President
        - Harper & Row, 1966-1971 (Box 281, Folder 16)
        - Cowles, 1966-1967 (Box 281, Folder 17)
        - Amendments to contract, 1967 (Box 281, Folder 18)
        - Germany, Greece, Portugal, Norway, Denmark, Sweden, France, Italy, Rumania, Yugosloavia, 1966-1967 (Box 281, Folder 19)
        - Holland, Finland, Spain, Japan, England, China, 1966-1968 (Box 281, Folder 20)
        - General Services Administration, 1974 (Box 281, Folder 21)
        - Miscellaneous documents, 1966 (Box 281, Folder 22)
      - Disturber of the Peace, 1961 (Box 282, Folder 1)
      - The Glory and the Dream, 1974-2002, undated (Box 282, Folder 2)
      - Goodbye, Darkness, 1979-1982 (Box 282, Folder 3)
      - Goodbye, Darkness, 1985-2002, undated (Box 282, Folder 4)
      - In Our Time, 1987 (Box 282, Folder 5)
      - The Last Lion: Visions of Glory, 1979-1983 (Box 282, Folder 6)
      - The Long Gainer, 1959 (Box 282, Folder 7)
      - One Brief Shining Moment, 1983-1984 (Box 282, Folder 8)
      - Portrait of a President, 1961-1967 (Box 282, Folder 9)
      - A Rockefeller Family Portrait, 1958-1959 (Box 282, Folder 10)
      - Shadow of the Monsoon, 1955-1968 (Box 282, Folder 11)
      - Television, 1954 (Box 282, Folder 12)
      - A World Lit Only by Fire, 19992, 2002, undated (Box 282, Folder 13)
    - Dept. of Motor Vehicles, Connecticut, title, 1994 (Box 282, Folder 14)
    - Estate of Sallie Manchester, 1981 (Box 282, Folder 15)
    - Lynch, Joseph, 1995-1997 (Box 282, Folder 16)
    - McGinnis, 1992-1996 (Box 282, Folder 17-18)
    - Piracy [Kennedy television mini-series]
      - Correspondence, 1983 (Box 282, Folder 19-20)
      - Correspondence, 1983, 1985, undated (Box 283, Folder 1-8)
      - Gadney, Reg, Kennedy, 1983 (Box 284, Folder 1)
      - Scripts and notes, 1983 (Box 284, Folder 2-4)
    - Power of attorney, 1953, undated (Box 284, Folder 5)
    - Weiner, Mildred, living will, 1976 (Box 284, Folder 6)
    - Wills
      - Manchester, Julia, 1981 (Box 284, Folder 7)
      - Manchester, William, 1971, 1989 (Box 284, Folder 8)
  - Longboat Key house-1, 1978 (Box 284, Folder 9-11)
  - Longboat Key house-2, 1979 (Box 284, Folder 12)
  - Longboat Key house-3, 1978-81 (Box 284, Folder 13-14)
  - Longboat Key house-4, 1979-81 (Box 285, Folder 1)
  - Longboat Key-dead file, 1978 (Box 285, Folder 2)
  - Manchester house paint and minor repairs, 1972 (Box 285, Folder 3)
  - Manchester-Mencken correspondence, 1968 (Box 285, Folder 4)
  - Manuals (Box 285, Folder 5)
  - Maps (Box 285, Folder 6)
  - Martha's Vineyard, house as an investment, 1972 (Box 285, Folder 7)
  - Materials tipped in books (Box 285, Folder 8-9)
  - Medical records
    - Mass. Mutual, 1966, 1968 (Box 285, Folder 10)
    - Medical insurance, 1967-75 and undated (Box 285, Folder 11)
    - Heart, bulk 1995 Jul-1996 Dec (Box 285, Folder 12)
    - 1995-96 (Box 285, Folder 13)
    - 1997-2004 and undated (Box 286, Folder 1)
  - Notebook, ca. 1950s (Box 286, Folder 2)
  - Notebook, 1963 (Box 286, Folder 3)
  - Notebook, 1970 (Box 286, Folder 4)
  - Notebook, undated (Box 286, Folder 5)
  - Notebook, undated (Box 286, Folder 6)
  - Notebook, undated (Box 286, Folder 7)
  - Notebook, undated (Box 286, Folder 8)
  - #10 [Downing Street], 1980-90 (Box 287, Folder 1)
  - Office files, ca. late 1980s-2000
    - Guide to files (Box 287, Folder 2)
    - Munich (Box 287, Folder 3)
    - Misc. notes (Box 287, Folder 4)
    - Misc. pages (Box 287, Folder 5)
    - Appraisal (Box 287, Folder 6)
    - Insurance (Box 287, Folder 7)
    - General (Box 287, Folder 8)
    - Now (Box 288, Folder 1-3)
    - Lion III contracts (Box 288, Folder 4-5)
    - Files (Box 288, Folder 6)
    - IRS (Box 288, Folder 7)
    - Wesleyan phone numbers (Box 288, Folder 8)
    - Agent and editors (Box 288, Folder 9)
    - Webster (Box 288, Folder 10)
    - Phone (Box 288, Folder 11)
    - Wesleyan (Box 288, Folder 12-14)
    - Correspondence (Box 288, Folder 15)
    - Contracts (Box 288, Folder 16)
    - Office maps (Box 288, Folder 17)
    - Word Perfect (Box 288, Folder 18)
    - Yale (Box 288, Folder 19)
    - Adminstration (Box 289, Folder 1)
    - Clintons (Box 289, Folder 2)
    - Word Perfect lists of files (Box 289, Folder 3)
    - H L M (Box 289, Folder 4)
    - Genealogy (Box 289, Folder 5)
    - Addresses and wallet card (Box 289, Folder 6)
    - Future projects (Box 289, Folder 7)
    - Future books (Box 289, Folder 8)
    - Film (Box 289, Folder 9)
    - Shawmut (Box 289, Folder 10)
    - Current writing income (Box 289, Folder 11)
    - Mercedes 340 (Box 289, Folder 12)
    - Miscellaneous disk files lists (19) (Box 289, Folder 13)
    - Recent books & files (Box 289, Folder 14)
    - Projects (Box 290, Folder 1)
    - Images (Box 290, Folder 2)
    - Wills & living wills (Box 290, Folder 3)
    - Health (Box 290, Folder 4)
    - Legal (Box 290, Folder 5-6)
    - Net (Box 290, Folder 7-8)
    - United States Marine Corps (Box 290, Folder 9)
    - Getting Laid (Box 291, Folder 1-2)
    - Unidentified (Box 291, Folder 3)
  - Passports (Box 291, Folder 4)
  - People to get books, 1989 (Box 291, Folder 5)
  - Personal miscellanous #2, 1946-73, undated (Box 291, Folder 6)
  - Pine St.-mortgage, ca. 1978 (Box 291, Folder 7)
  - Presidential dinner, 1995 Aug 8 (Box 291, Folder 8)
  - Reaching the People, 1994 (Box 291, Folder 9-10)
  - The Red Lion (Box 291, Folder 11)
  - Reviews, 1951-92 (Box 291, Folder 12)
  - Reviews (book), 1951-92 (Box 292, Folder 1)
  - Reviews-best of 1988 (Box 292, Folder 2)
  - Roberts, Jimm, poster, 1995 (Box shelf)
  - Society of American Historians, 1978-80 (Box 292, Folder 3)
  - Speeches
    - John Hopkins University, 1951 (Box 292, Folder 4)
    - Mount Saint Agnes College, 1951 (Box 292, Folder 5)
    - Enoch Pratt Free Library, 1952 (Box 292, Folder 6)
    - The Phoenix Club, 1952 (Box 292, Folder 7)
    - Enoch Pratt Free Library, 1954 (Box 292, Folder 8)
    - Wesleyan University, 1959 (Box 292, Folder 9)
    - Untitled, ca. 1950s (Box 292, Folder 10)
    - Wesleyan University, 1960 (Box 292, Folder 11)
    - University of Massachusetts, 1962 (Box 292, Folder 12)
    - Wesleyan University, 1963 (Box 292, Folder 13)
    - Wesleyan University, 1966 (Box 292, Folder 14)
    - Recreating History, ca. 1967 (Box 292, Folder 15)
    - Enoch Pratt Free Library, 1968 (Box 292, Folder 16-17)
    - Oral History Association, 1968 (Box 292, Folder 18-20)
    - Oral History and Anatomy of a Novelist lectures, ca. 1969 (Box 292, Folder 21)
    - 58th Chicago Sun-Times book week luncheon, 1969 (Box 292, Folder 22)
    - Hollins Conference on Creative Writing and Cinema, 1969-70 (Box 292, Folder 23-24)
    - Hollins Conference on Creative Writing and Cinema, 1969-70 (Box 293, Folder 1)
    - Richmond Book & Author Dinner, 1976 (Box 293, Folder 2)
    - Wesleyan University, 1978 (Box 293, Folder 3)
    - Brigham Young University, 1979-80 (Box 293, Folder 4)
    - University of Massachusetts, 1980 (Box 293, Folder 5)
    - Wesleyan University, 1980 (Box 293, Folder 6)
    - Oklahoma Bar Association, 1984 (Box 293, Folder 7)
    - Yale Political Union, 1984 (Box 293, Folder 8-9)
    - Hofstra University, 1985 (Box 293, Folder 10)
    - International Churchill Society, 1986 (Box 293, Folder 11)
    - Untitled, ca. 1987 (Box 293, Folder 12)
    - Amherst, 1989 (Box 293, Folder 13)
    - Wesleyan University, 1992 (Box 293, Folder 14)
    - The Baltimore Evening Sun wake, 1995 (Box 293, Folder 15)
    - University of Southern Carolina, 1995 (Box 293, Folder 16)
    - Krupp, undated (Box 293, Folder 17)
    - MacArthur, undated (Box 293, Folder 18)
    - Mencken, undated (Box 293, Folder 19)
    - Rotary Club of Middletown, undated (Box 293, Folder 20)
    - That's Our Weakness Now, undated (Box 294, Folder 1)
    - William Shirer tribute, undated (Box 294, Folder 2)
  - Stanmar + ferry, 1972 (Box 294, Folder 3)
  - Stanmar-Martha's Vineyard, 1970, 1972 (Box 294, Folder 4)
  - Stationery and business cards, William Manchester (Box 294, Folder 5-6)
  - Stationery, Washington, D.C. (Box 294, Folder 7-8)
  - Stationery, others (Box 294, Folder 9-10)
  - System to beat roulette, undated (Box 295, Folder 1)
  - Three After Six interview transcript, 1967 Apr 18 (Box 295, Folder 2)
  - 316 Pine Street files, circa 1990s
    - JFK assassination (Box 295, Folder 3)
    - Invitations (Box 295, Folder 4)
    - Service contracts (Box 295, Folder 5)
    - Toshiba data (Box 295, Folder 6)
    - Magellan manuscript (Box 295, Folder 7)
    - Manuals (Box 295, Folder 8)
    - Kennedy (Box 295, Folder 9)
    - To do (Box 295, Folder 10)
    - Florida (Box 295, Folder 11)
    - Addresses (Box 295, Folder 12)
    - Biographical information (Box 295, Folder 13)
    - Computer (Box 295, Folder 14)
    - Tape #2 WM Ch (Box 295, Folder 15)
    - Essays (Box 295, Folder 16)
    - Awards (Box 296, Folder 1)
    - Book notes (Box 296, Folder 2)
    - Churchill (Box 296, Folder 3)
    - Churchill conference Boston, 1995 Oct (Box 296, Folder 4)
    - Insurance (Box 296, Folder 5)
    - Lancer-Kennedy (Box 296, Folder 6)
  - Travel
    - 1970-79 (Box 296, Folder 7)
    - 1990-96 (Box 296, Folder 8)
    - England, 1967 (Box 296, Folder 9)
    - England, 1973 (Box 296, Folder 10)
    - Fort Burt, 1970 (Box 296, Folder 11)
    - Holland, 1975-76 (Box 296, Folder 12)
    - Little Dix Bay, 1968 (Box 296, Folder 13)
    - London, 1966-80 (Box 296, Folder 14)
    - London, 1969 (Box 297, Folder 1)
    - Martha's Vineyard, 1969 (Box 297, Folder 2)
    - Mexico, 1959-60 (Box 297, Folder 3)
    - Puerto Rico, 1971 (Box 297, Folder 4)
    - Tortola, 1970 (Box 297, Folder 5)
  - University of Massachusetts
    - 1968 (Box 297, Folder 6)
    - Friends of the Library, 1970-74 (Box 297, Folder 7-9)
    - Gift, 1982-83 (Box 297, Folder 10)
    - Fortieth reunion, 1984 (Box 297, Folder 11)
    - Fiftieth reunion, 1995 (Box 297, Folder 12)
  - United States Marine Corps. (Box 297, Folder 13-14)
  - Veterans Administration, 2001 (Box 297, Folder 15)
  - Victory of the Soviet people in the great patriotic war, 1965-84 (Box 297, Folder 16)
  - Wesleyan University
    - Wesleyan 2, 1968-69 (Box 298, Folder 1-2)